ogero.gov.lb 2017-05-28

# OGERO - Privacy Policy

**This website is owned and run by OGERO Telecom.**

OGERO is committed to protecting and safeguarding your Privacy. 

We promise to protect your privacy and information in line with this privacy policy 

The data you give us about yourself will enable OGERO to send you updates and provide you with services you have requested. We may use your e-mail address to contact you.   
We will not share your information with any other company.   
At any time, you can let us know if you do not want to receive any information. 

We use website links to improve our site.  These links are clearly identified to make you aware that you are leaving our website.  Please be mindful of the fact that these websites are not owned and maintained by OGERO.  They are run by other companies and organisations and we can therefore not accept any responsibility for any personal information you choose to divulge to them.  They will adhere to their own privacy policies. 

 Normally, we receive information about you in two ways: 

  1. Directly from you :   
For instance when you register your details with us, we record the information you provide us with.   

  2. Indirectly from you:   
For example, information whilst visiting our website, or details relating to transactions you enter into with us or others through our company. 

    * Our privacy policy sets out what happens to your personal information.  Because we are constantly updating and reviewing our service to you, there may be developments in how we use your data. 

    * We will promptly notify you of any changes with a link to this Privacy Policy on the log-in page of this site.  We may change your privacy policy and therefore encourage you to come back to this page occasionally / encourage you to check our website under 'Privacy Policy' occasionally.
